<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TestingApp</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Map</string>
    <string name="lviv_description">The de facto capital of Ukraine’s folksy west, history-rich Lviv is a world away from most travellers’ notion of a post-Soviet city. Forever promising to become the next Prague or Kraków, this million-strong Austro-Hungarian gem, packed with a millennium of churches, a huddle of bean-perfumed coffee houses and Eastern Europe’s quirkiest bunch of restaurants, has been on the verge of bursting onto the international tourism stage for decades.\n

        Following the recent political changes in these parts, this seductive Ukrainian diva may just be about to enter stage left. And Ukraine’s about-turn to the West is not the only thing making right now a great time to pay Lviv a visit. Following the devaluation of the Ukrainian currency, the hryvnya, never before has Ukraine been more affordable as a destination (a tram ride costs the equivalent of six US cents, a cup of coffee 80 US cents). But is it safe? Well, many travellers turning up in Lviv since the start of the conflict in Ukraine’s east have been surprised to find a city on the up, its famous cafes and restaurants packed and nary a Kalashnikov in sight.\n
        The international bean-frenzy has crept across Eastern Europe in a rash of cloned cafes, but Lviv is different. A reluctant part of the USSR for only 50 years, this Habsburg city managed to retain its Viennese caffeine traditions and the result is the best line-up of coffee houses in Eastern Europe, some roasting and grinding their own blends. September’s coffee festival pays homage to western Ukraine’s best brews, but if you pitch up in Lviv any other time, Svit Kavy near the Latin Cathedral is a traditional coffee house where the focus is firmly on heart-pumping roasts. For a fun but equally tasty take on Lviv’s percolated customs, head for Lvivska Kopalnya Kavy, literally the ‘Lviv Coffee Mine’ right on the main square – ploshcha Rynok. Beneath this traditional dark-wood Austrian-era coffee house is where Lviv’s stratum of arabica is mined; you can visit colliers at the bean-face before heading back upstairs for a fragrant cuppa.</string>
</resources>
